<?xml version="1.0"?>
<storyline>
<chapter>
<d img="0_0.jpg">In the distant future, mankind will go extinct leaving Doggos as the most prosperous creature.</d>
<d img="0_1.jpg">Doggos of all shapes and sizes will possess talents no humans could dream of having today.</d>
<d img="0_2.jpg">A company called DOGGO NEEDS INC. will have a monopoly over almost everything.</d>
<d img="0_3.jpg">At the same time Doggos will live in a most captivating futuristic world.</d>
<d>But one Doggo will almost completely surpass the rest.</d>
<d>And his name will of course be..... Doggo.</d>
<d>Doggo woke up. They'd been staying at the K-9 hotel now for longer than they'd hoped.</d>
<d>Doggo stared out the window at the sun long enough for it to harm his health.</d>
<d>It was a perfect day for a walk.</d>
<d img="0_4.jpg">Doggo dug up his old robot and had it walk it at its pace of choice.</d>
<d img="0_5.jpg">Not long after they'd started, they got hungry.</d>
<d>Fortunately they were only about a block away from their favorite supplier of treats, DOGGO NEEDS INC.</d>
<d>Doggo waltzed into the store exhausted from the walk, and started searching for treats.</d>
<d>On display near the center of the shop was a treat labeled "THE ULTIMATE TASTY TREAT".</d>
<d>Doggo stared at it for awhile. It appeared to glow.</d>
<d img="0_6.jpg">Signs surrounded the display. "Remember citizens of 'DOGGO NEEDS' district; all thieves regardless of crime will be TICKLED TO THEIR DOOM".</d>
<d img="0_7.jpg">Without thinking, Doggo stole the treat. It was odd because up to this point he'd been a model citizen.</d>
<d>He also stole a car parked outside the shop, and soon him and his robot dog were in a high speed chase with a bunch of cops.</d>
</chapter>
<chapter>
<d>Doggo had escaped the police for the time being...</d>
<d>He and his "dog" had hidden in a place so barren, so bleak, and so derelict that the police would not find them there.</d>
<d>It seemed like a perfect place to hide, but even so they could not stay there long.</d>
<d>It lacked most of the basic needs of living things.</d>
<d>When Doggo ventured far enough across this land, he came across something completely unexpected.</d>
<d>There was a building with a group of doggos inside.</d>
<d>"Hey! Who's out there?!", one of them yelled.</d>
<d>Doggo figured he would answer since he had nothing to lose.</d>
<d>"My name's Doggo. I'm here because I'm hiding from DOGGO NEEDS. I stole a treat".</d>
<d>Only then did Doggo realize DOGGO NEEDS rewarded citizens who helped them catch criminals.</d>
<d>Doggo wasn't very bright. "Wait!! please don't turn me in!".</d>
<d>"It's okay", one of the other doggos spoke. "We're all criminals too. We help each other".</d>
<d>And so, Doggo joined the unnamed revolutionary group without knowing what was to come...</d>
</chapter>
<chapter>
<d>The only problem Doggo had with the group's ideals was that members couldn't leave the group. Rule number twenty nine was: "once a member, always a member".</d>
<d>No matter what happened, members of the group faced every problem encountered together. Besides this, however, Doggo enjoyed having someone to watch their back.</d>
<d>The group had no leader, so they simply decided what they would do next together. Doggo seemed to have a lot of influence since he was a new member.</d>
<d>Every time they left the desert land they were chased by the doggo police. They left the desert land a lot so they could get food and water.</d>
<d>Sometimes they drove on the wrong side of the road to escape them, but then it was almost impossible to escape crashing.</d>
<d>The group didn't believe they had the power to vanquish DOGGO NEEDS, but they had to be strong enough to survive and defy the monopoly's rule at the same time.</d>
</chapter>
<chapter>
<d>Doggo ends up getting all the treats he wants, but the catch is that he can't eat any of them.</d>
<d>The Doggo police all retire as there is no need to enforce the law.</d>
<d>DOGGO NEEDS INC. loses its monopoly on everything, and eventually goes out of business.</d>
<d>The revolutionary group members are unsatisfied with what happened to DOGGO NEEDS, and continue to annoy its founders.</d>
<d>Other random civilians find a new enjoyment in their everyday lives.</d>
<d>After Doggo made it clear he wasn't dedicated to the cause and broke rule number twenty nine, the group gave chase.</d>
<d>Doggo has been driving ever since...</d>
</chapter>
</storyline>